[
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "With which among the following sports, Ian Thorpe is related to?",
        "correct": "Swimming",
        "incorrect": ["Racing", "Boxing", "Athletics"]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which Football Club was designated as the FIFA Club of the Century in 2000?",
        "correct": "Real Madrid",
        "incorrect": ["Liverpool", "Arsenal", "Manchester United"]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which Indian athlete is known as the “Queen of Indian Track and Field” or “Golden Girl”?",
        "correct": "P T Usha",
        "incorrect": ["Kamaljeet Sandhu", "Sunita Rani", "Krishna Punia"]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "How many team members are there in each team of an ice hockey game?",
        "correct": "6",
        "incorrect": ["8", "10", "12"]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What is the national sport of India?",
        "correct": "Hockey",
        "incorrect": ["Football", "Cricket", "Badminton"]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "2014 FIFA World Cup will be held in?",
        "correct": "Brazil",
        "incorrect": ["Canada", "Japan", "london"]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The First Asian Games was held in which country?",
        "correct": "India",
        "incorrect": ["japan", "Bhutan", "Nepal"]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "How many players play in a Kabaddi team",
        "correct": "7",
        "incorrect": ["8", "12", "4"]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which is the national sport of Japan?",
        "correct": "Judo",
        "incorrect": ["Football", "Baseball", "Chess"]
    },
    {
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "2018 FIFA World Cup would be held in?",
        "correct": "Russia",
        "incorrect": ["Qatar", "Brazil", "South africa"]
    }
]